Calvin Choe

1869 Beech St Knoxvile, TN 37920

(901) 212-9826 calvinchoe1@gmail.com

Skills:

- PHP
- Drupal/Wordpress
- Laravel
- MySQL/MariaDB
- Javascript/Vue.js
- Debian-based and RHEL OS
- Docker
- Bash scripting
- Git
- HTML/CSS
- Python
- UI/UX design
- Accessibility

Platforms:

- Digital Ocean
- AWS
- Pantheon Web Hosting

Summary

I am a full-stack developer specializing in traditional LAMP stacks with newer front-end technologies such as Vue.js. I enjoy taking the needs of people and creating software that can match those needs. The changing landscape of software is also exciting to be a part of and being able to leverage ever-improving technology helps to solve issues more effectively, thereby constantly improving the quality of software that I create.

Education

Corporate Finance & Accounting

University of TN, Knoxville, Aug 2013 - Dec 2017

Experience

Senior Web Developer

Sept 2019 - Present

The Beef Jerky Experience, Inc.

- Ordering system to allow franchisees to purchase product from vendors and purchase order system to assist in receiving shipments and correctly updating inventory
- Financial analysis tool that extracts franchisee data from the POS company's REST API to allow anonymous benchmarking
- Various enhancements to the base e-commerce bundle--BJE gift card payments, Rewards point redemptions, specialized built-in promotions, donations, and more to support a 7-figure revenue website
- Changes to improve WCAG compliance for accessibility

Back-end Developer

Nov 2018 – Aug 2019

Charles Tombras Advertising

- Maintained existing web applications written in Joomla, Wordpress, and Drupal
- Assisted in ADA compliance measures for clients
- Wrote REST APIs to expose relevant data for integration with other applications

Web Developer/IT Specialist

Feb 2018 – Nov 2018

The Beef Jerky Outlet, Inc.

- Maintain existing Drupal e-commerce website for 80+ storefronts including bug fixing and additional PHP development
- Manage and administrate suite of enterprise services used for ecommerce and normal retail business including Office 365,
 Microsoft Sharepoint, and other SaaS-related services